The Scary of Sixty-First is a horror, mystery,
thriller film directed by Dasha Nekrasova.
Two roommates’ lives are upended after finding out that their
new Manhattan apartment harbors a dark secret.
Addie, played by Betsey Brown.
Noelle, played by Madeline Quinn.
The Girl, played by Dasha Nekrasova.
Greg, played by Mark H. Rapaport.
Apothecary Clerk, played by Jason Grisell.
The Realtor, played by Stephen Gurewitz.
The Scary of Sixty-First is a 2021 American horror thriller exploitation film directed by Dasha
Nekrasova (in her feature directorial debut), who co-wrote the screenplay with Madeline Quinn.
It stars Betsey Brown, Quinn, and Dasha Nekrasova.
The film had its world premiere in the Encounters section of the 71st Berlin
International Film Festival, where it won the Best First Feature Award.
In May 2021, distribution rights were acquired by
distributor Utopia and streaming service Shudder.
It opened in theaters in Los Angeles on December 3, 2021, and in New York
City on December 17, followed by a VOD release on December 24.
The film explores themes of exploitation, possession,
lesbian sex, occult, manhattan, new york city.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.